<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Inverse</string>
    <string name="lore">The Knight arrives at the ruins of Hallownest, and makes camp at the small town of Dirtmouth just above its entrance. As the Knight ventures through the ruins, they discover that Hallownest was once a flourishing kingdom which fell to ruin after becoming overrun with &quot;The Infection&quot;, which drove its citizens to madness and undeath. The last ruler of Hallownest, the Pale King, attempted to seal away the Infection; however, it becomes increasingly clear that the seal is failing.
        \n\nThe Knight is granted the power to enter the dreams of certain powerful entities; this allows the Knight to find and kill the three Dreamers who act as living locks to the seal. This quest brings the Knight into conflict with &quot;Hornet&quot;, a female warrior who acts as the &quot;protector&quot; of Hallownest and who tests the Knight\s resolve in several battles.
        \n\nThrough dialogue with certain characters as well as cutscenes, the Knight receives insight into the origin of the Infection and itself. In ancient times, the bugs of Hallownest worshiped a higher being called the Radiance: a primordial, god-like moth whose mere presence could sway the denizens of Hallownest to mindless obedience. One day, another higher being called The Wyrm arrived at Hallownest, and transformed into the Pale King so that it could establish a grand kingdom.
        \n\nThe Pale King &quot;expanded&quot; the minds of the bugs of Hallownest, granting them intelligence and self-awareness, and eliminated The Radiance by destroying all memory of it; devoid of worship, the Radiance faded away. This lasted until an ancient statue of The Radiance was accidentally unearthed during an excavation, reviving her memory: enraged, The Radiance began invading the dreams of Hallownest\s citizens and driving them to madness, an affliction known as The Infection.
        \n\nIn an attempt to contain the spreading Infection, the Pale King used the power of Void (a type of living darkness) to create the Vessels: living yet empty beings that would hypothetically lack a will which could be corrupted by The Infection. After many attempts, he created a suitable Vessel (the Hollow Knight) and used it to contain the Infection, then sealed the Hollow Knight within the Black Egg Temple with the aid of the three Dreamers. Yet because the Pale King had bonded with The Hollow Knight as a parent and child (respectively), the Hollow Knight developed a &quot;wish&quot; that was used by The Radiance as a foothold for corruption, compromising the seal.
        \n\nAs the story progresses, the Knight discovers that they are a failed Vessel: one of hundreds who failed to be chosen as the Hollow Knight, yet had the strength to escape The Abyss from which all Void originates."</string>
    <string name="default_error">An unexpected error occurred, please try again later</string>
    <string name="content_description">Hollow knight image</string>
</resources>